people often ask me for
guidance on how to make the transition
from their lifestyle to the countryside
i cannot give any advice that applies to
everyone and so i'm reticent to give any
at all
you know your own situation best and i
will leave resources down below that may
be useful to you
however i want to offer you a
perspective that may be helpful
in a different way i hope it can bring
comfort to you
as you try to change your life or
encourage you to embrace your current
[Music]
situation making a move to a rural area
isn't feasible or practical for everyone
for example i was lucky to be
able-bodied and young
and find a job within my skill set that
gives me a livable wage
those can be hard to come by for
millennials like myself
however you can bring so much of what
you love about another way of life into
your own reality without making the
physical move
and it is just as rich and meaningful
[Music]
think about where you live maybe it's a
cozy city apartment
a town or the countryside wherever you
are
imagine that that is exactly where you
need to be at this point
in your personal story stories don't
begin at the end
they present the hero's journey from one
place to another
physically or internally this is
something that has truly helped me on my
path to change my life
comforted me when i felt stuck but to
also see the worth in the process of
taking months
years or decades to get to where i want
to go
at 19 i was a student living in a
condemnable
infested apartment right next to a
highway
i deeply disliked where i lived and i
would cry myself to sleep some nights
because adult life was nothing like i
imagined it to be
i was lonely and tired of being a
student staying awake all night studying
only to have to go to my job as a
magazine editor
the next day my dreams of a quiet
peaceful life in the countryside seemed
completely out of reach
i was burned out and unhealthy in both
mind and body
if you've ever been there you know that
one of the most dangerous parts of
feeling that way
is that you think it will last forever
and believe tomorrow will be no
different
and for a time i did give in and i
despaired
and then one day i decided that my
despair was a lie
and asked for help ever so slowly things
got better
and i started to feel again
[Music]
so
those were hard years but looking back
it clarified what i wanted out of life
what i needed and what i had to change
in my mentality in order to succeed
was it a happy time no but life doesn't
need to always be happy in order to be
fruitful
i had to look within and examine the
source of my feelings
living in the future was ruining my
present
i started taking practical steps towards
the life i wanted
saving and researching and applying to
jobs
i had to work hard for years to make my
dreams come true
but the hardest part was learning to be
satisfied where i currently was
i needed to know that i could build a
wonderful life whether or not things
were perfect
only then would i be ready to make the
move successfully
and to be happy
[Music]
many of us will experience living in at
least a couple different places in our
lives
maybe you love where you live maybe you
want to live somewhere else
whatever your situation is i encourage
you to embrace your current location and
pour your love into living your best
life
if that seems hard find little ways to
appreciate your place in the steps you
take
in order to plan for the future for
example
if you love your home in the city but
miss nature you can adopt plants and
make it a space full of life
no matter where you are you can live
more sustainably and in alignment with
the seasons
instead of wishing to fulfill a future
dream try to live a version of it in the
meantime
imperfect yes but that's how life is
it challenges us to simply enjoy
existing
i have lived in the city the countryside
and in between
each place has benefits and suits
different personalities
and can lead to a wonderful story i like
to think that with the right mindset
you can cultivate contentment in most
places assuming that your basic needs
are met of course you may not be
in your ideal location maybe it's a
stepping stone that will offer you many
opportunities to learn and grow in the
process
either way your thoughts and insights
are always appreciated and helpful to
all of us
feel free to comment your experience
down below i wish you all the best
in trying to change improve or simply
love your life and location
even more take care
okay
[Music]
thank you
you